Uh-huh.
嗯嗯。
Bonjour, Mademoiselle Sandy.
你好，桑迪小姐。
I have brought your usual,
我带来了你平常的，
one Krusty Kombo.
一份 Krusty Kombo。
Thanks, SpongeBob.
谢谢，海绵宝宝。
But I won't
be needing the food.
但我不会
需要食物。
I brought a little something
of my own from home...
我带了一点东西
我自己从家里...
From home,
from home, from home.
从家里，
从家里，从家里。
Sandy's smokin' barbecue nuts!
桑迪的烧烤坚果！
I see nothing!
我什么也没看见！
There is no outside food
allowed at the Krusty Krab.
没有外面的食物
蟹堡王允许。
Come on, SpongeBob.
来吧，海绵宝宝。
I won't spill the nuts
if you won't.
我不会把坚果洒出来
如果你不这样做。
Mmm.
嗯。
Perfecto!
完美！
I haven't seen a thing.
我什么也没看到。
Try one.
尝试一个。
Mm.
Ooh...
毫米。
哦...
wh...
什...
Hm?
嗯？
Whoo!
Now that's what I call
呼！
现在这就是我所说的
Texas heat!
德克萨斯州炎热！
But we really should stop
before Mr. Krabs finds out.
但我们真的应该停下来
在蟹老板发现之前。
Hm?
嗯？
Hmm.
唔。
Finds out what?
发现了什么？
Yikes!
哎呀！
Oh, uh, hi, Mr. Krabs.
哦，呃，嗨，蟹老板。
Outside food!
外面的食物！
Oh, mercy, Mr. Krabs!
哦，天哪，蟹老板！
She knows not
the error of her ways!
她不知道
她的做法是错误的！
Oh, please.
哦，拜托。
I bet one taste of these nuts
我打赌尝过这些坚果的味道
and you'll whistle
a different tune!
你会吹口哨
不同的曲调！
That's enough!
够了！
I'm confiscerating
these unauthorized acorns.
我没收
这些未经授权的橡子。
Eh, what's so good about these
unauthorized nuts anyway?
呃，这些有什么好处
无论如何，未经授权的坚果？
Hmm.
嗯。
All right!
好的！
Sandy, you're hired!
桑迪，你被录用了！
To do what?
做什么？
Whoa!
哇！
Why, to make those nuts
at me restaurant, of course.
为什么，要做那些坚果
当然是在我的餐厅。
They're delicirous!
它们很好吃！
Uh, you're a few pickles shy
of a Krabby Patty
呃，你有点害羞
蟹肉饼
if you think
I'm looking for a job.
如果你认为
我正在找工作。
Sandy, this is no mere job!
桑迪，这不仅仅是工作！
This is a calling.
这是一个呼召。
This is a duty to serve.
这是一种服务的义务。
This is a dream come true.
这是梦想成真。
Well, shoot!
Why not?
好吧，射击！
为什么不呢？
But I'll need me
a barbecue grill.
但我需要我
烧烤架
No problem.
没问题。
I got an old Navy trick
for makeshift barbecues.
我有一个海军老把戏
用于临时烧烤。
Ta-da!
哒哒！
Not too shabby.
不太破旧。
I reckon she'll do.
我想她会的。
Make sure to show her
the ropes, boy-o!
一定要给她看
绳索，男孩哦！
Barbecue nuts?
烧烤坚果？
These customers will
eat anything.
这些客户将
吃任何东西。
Mmm.
Nice aftertaste.
嗯。
回味不错。
♪ Sandy's in the kitchen
with SpongeBob ♪
♪ 桑迪在厨房里
和海绵宝宝一起♪
♪ We're in the kitchen,
we two ♪
♪ 我们在厨房里，
我们两个♪
♪ Sandy's in the kitchen
with SpongeBob ♪
♪ 桑迪在厨房里
和海绵宝宝一起♪
♪ Makin' nuts on the barbecue ♪
♪ 在烧烤上做坚果 ♪
You heard the boss man.
你听到了老板的声音。
Tell me what's what.
告诉我那是什么。
Well, this here is
where the magic happens,
嗯，这里是
魔法发生的地方，
the grill.
烤架。
Yeow!
哟！
As long as the sacred space
is respected,
只要神圣空间
受到尊重，
the kitchen will remain
in perfect harmony.
厨房将保留
完美和谐。
Not to worry!
不用担心！
We'll be like two crickets
on a fiddle in here--
我们会像两只蟋蟀
在这里拉小提琴——
Huh?
啊？
Here.
Knock yourselves out,
这里。
把自己打垮，
please.
请。
Already on it!
已经开始了！
So how many nuts
should I fix up?
那么有多少坚果
我应该修复吗？
Nuts?
坚果？
Oh, sorry, Sandy.
There must be a mistake.
哦，对不起，桑迪。
肯定弄错了。
These are all
for Krabby Patties.
这些都是
蟹肉饼。
- Oh.
- Don't worry!
- 哦。
- 不用担心！
I'll get the word out!
我会把话说出来！
Howdy, Bubble Bass!
你好，泡泡巴斯！
I reckon you're hankering
for a delicious new dish!
我猜你正在渴望
一道美味的新菜！
Certainly not.
当然不是。
I procure
the same patty every day
我采购
每天都吃同样的馅饼
because I have a refined--
因为我有一个精致的——
Ooh!
哦！
Such smoky sapidity.
如此烟熏味。
What is it?
它是什么？
Sandy's smokin'
barbecue nuts!
桑迪在抽烟
烧烤坚果！
Pretty good, am I right?
很好，我说得对吗？
Not just pretty good,
不仅表现得很好，
but good enough to go on...
但足够继续下去了...
the big screen!
大屏幕！
"Try Sandy's smokin'
barbecue nuts."
“试试桑迪的抽烟”
烧烤坚果。”
You hear that, everyone?
大家听到了吗？
This guy's butt loves
those nuts!
这家伙的屁股真爱
那些疯子！
I'll take some nuts!
我要吃点坚果！
His butt's never wrong!
他的屁股永远不会错！
- I want some!
- Me too!
- 我想要一些！
- 我也是！
Ooh, nuts!
哦，疯了！
Whoo, doggy!
哇，狗仔！
Now we're cookin'!
现在我们开始做饭了！
Yeah!
是的！
Uh...
呃...
Ah.
啊。
Mmm.
嗯。
Hm.
both: Yah!
两人：啊！
Here.
这里。
Aww.
哇。
Hup! Hup! Hup!
哈！哈！哈！
Hmm?
唔？
Ohh-up.
哦，上。
Ha.
哈。
- Huh?
- Demand for nuts is up.
- 啊？
- 对坚果的需求增加。
- Uh...
- So we're increasing supply!
- 呃...
- 所以我们正在增加供应！
- Bah.
- Make way, boy-o.
- 呸。
- 让路，小伙子。
Well, gee, Mr. Krabs,
好吧，哎呀，蟹老板先生，
I think you might be
overwhelming poor Sandy.
我想你可能是
压倒性的可怜的桑迪。
Hmph!
哼！
Ha!
哈!
This here's
the barbecue lunch rush!
这是这里的
烧烤午餐高峰期！
And, uh, here.
还有，呃，这里。
Somebody wants
a Krabby Patty, I guess.
有人想要
我猜是蟹肉饼。
- Hm.
- Now giddyup!
- 嗯。
- 现在头晕目眩！
Whoa!
哇！
Ah!
啊!
Phew!
唷！
All the orders are up.
所有的订单都到齐了。
Yep.
All of 'em.
是的。
他们所有人。
Ooh, that one's mine.
哦，那个是我的。
Mm... perfect!
嗯...完美！
No more wobble.
不再晃动。
Patty.
帕蒂。
Don't you love the new look?
你不喜欢新外观吗？
I'm just here for the nuts.
我只是来找坚果的。
Kowboy Krab's Nut Shack?
Kowboy Krab 的坚果小屋？
Pfft, it's full of nuts,
all right.
噗，里面全是坚果，
好吧。
SpongeBob, hand me them tongs
over there, will ya?
海绵宝宝，把夹子递给我
在那儿，好吗？
I'm busier than a six-legged
horse in tap shoes!
我比六足人还忙
穿踢踏鞋的马！
Ooh!
Thanks, SpongeBob!
哦！
谢谢，海绵宝宝！
Must breathe.
必须呼吸。
Ohh.
哦。
There's gold
in them there nuts!
有金子
他们里面有坚果！
What's in the bags,
Mr. Krabs?
袋子里装的是什么
蟹老板？
Oh, this here's the next
round of barbecue nut orders.
哦，这是下一个
一轮烧烤坚果订单。
Ooh.
哦。
Well, scratch my back
and call me a cactus!
嗯，挠我的背
并叫我仙人掌！
And what about that one?
那那个呢？
Oh, this one?
哦，这个？
This one's full of useless
Krabby Patties.
这个充满了无用的东西
蟹肉饼。
Nobody really wants 'em,
so they're garbage.
没有人真正想要他们，
所以它们是垃圾。
Oh, my!
哦，天哪！
SpongeBob!
海绵宝宝！
Hi, Sandy.
嗨，桑迪。
Just toasting my buns. Heh.
只是烤我的面包。呵呵。
Move over, lad.
You're blocking me trash.
走过去，小伙子。
你挡住了我的垃圾。
Money, money, money, money.
Nuts, nuts, nuts.
钱，钱，钱，钱。
坚果，坚果，坚果。
Uh, SpongeBob?
呃，海绵宝宝？
Are you gonna be okay?
你会没事吗？
Back to work.
返回工作岗位。
That money won't
barbecue itself!
这笔钱不会
烧烤本身！
Ah, I love the smell
of money.
啊，我喜欢这个味道
钱。
Little smokier than usual.
比平时烟味大一点。
Ohh, yeah.
哦，是的。
Huh?
啊？
Mr. Squidward,
what's the holdup?
章鱼哥先生，
有什么阻碍吗？
Why don't you ask
your pitmaster?
你为什么不问
你的坑主？
She stopped barbecuing nuts.
她不再烧烤坚果了。
She what?
她什么？
Land dweller!
陆地居民！
What's the meaning of this?
这有什么意义呢？
Ohh.
哦。
I'm plumb out of nuts.
我已经疯了。
You're plumb out of what?
你是因为什么而铅垂的？
Sorry, Kowboy Krabs.
对不起，Kowboy Krabs。
Looks like you have to find
another way to make your dough.
看来你必须找到
另一种制作面团的方法。
So long, folks!
再见，伙计们！
- Uhh...
- The nut tree's done run dry!
- 呃...
- 坚果树已经干枯了！
Uh, howdy, y'all.
呃，你们好。
I don't reckon we can get no
Sandy's smokin' barbecue nuts
我不认为我们能得到
桑迪的烟熏烧烤坚果
without no Sandy, can we?
没有桑迪，我们可以吗？
Um... no.
嗯...不。
Riot!
暴动！
Yah!
- Whoa!
啊！
- 哇！
Huh?
Aah!
啊？
啊啊！
Huh?
啊？
Hey, everybody!
嘿，大家！
This table's got
that smoky Texas tang!
这张桌子有
德克萨斯州的烟熏汤！
Fascinating.
迷人。
The smoke from Sandy's nuts
has flavored
桑迪坚果冒出的烟
有味道
everything in this restaurant!
这家餐厅的一切！
Chow time!
周时间！
Mmm.
嗯。
No!
Stop it!
不！
停下来！
Me restaurant!
我的餐厅！
No!
不！
Huh?
啊？
Say, that smells delicious.
说吧，味道真香。
Oh, this?
哦，这个？
Oh, it's just a useless
old Krabby Patty.
呵呵，这只是一个无用的东西
老克拉比帕蒂。
A snack without splinters.
没有碎片的零食。
How novel.
多么新颖啊。
Perhaps we could partake
in your patties?
也许我们可以参加
在你的肉饼里？
Oh, hey,
I want some of those.
哦，嘿，
我想要其中一些。
Huh?
啊？
Orders up!
订单上架！
Good news!
好消息！
Trashy Patties are now
double the price!
现在是垃圾馅饼
价格翻倍！
Whoa!
哇！
Not so fast.
没那么快。
I reckon these patties
are on the house.
我认为这些肉饼
都在房子上。
Right, SpongeBob?
对吧，海绵宝宝？
Mm...
毫米...
all: Yeehaw!
全体：耶哈！
I guess we all went
a little nuts today.
我想我们都去了
今天有点疯狂。
Huh.
Still a nice aftertaste.
呵呵。
还是回味不错。